[music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful
um Monday afternoon. God bless everyone
in the name of Jesus Yeshua the Messiah.
We are live. You can see we got the
weighted vest on today, y'all. We got
the dang weighted vest on today. All
right. And Bitcoin is in straight up
chop city.
Straight up chop city. Guys, make sure
to smash the dang likes,
you know. Make sure to smash up the dang
likes, guys. Follow moment to the dang
like button. Make sure to share the
stream on Twitter and all this stuff.
Um, I think what do we have today? Do we
have I think we have a super chat goal.
I mean, I I don't know actually if we
have super chat goals or not in here,
but it was a new option I saw. And what
what did it say? If we can get how many
super chats in 45 minutes, we'll do a
$500 giveaway. Why not? It could be the
It could be a 99 cent super chat. All
right, so let's see. Let's see what
happens, guys. I just took a little bit
of a short scalp here. You can see I've
just taken a bit of a short scalp on
Bitcoin. The reason being, guys, is
simply because we came up to the naked
monthly point of control here.
I'm not expecting the biggest move to
the downside right now. But I wouldn't
be surprised if we don't come down to
like 63,520,
right? I wouldn't be surprised if we
don't come down to 63520. Let's go ahead
and set a little bit of an alert at
63520.
All right,
let's see. you know, not the worst move
in the world, not the best move in the
world, but yeah, guys, and another
thing, make sure to follow me on
Twitter. All right, big shout out to
everyone in here. Make sure to follow me
on Twitter. Make sure to share the
stream on Twitter. I mean, who wouldn't
want to follow me on Twitter? Your
strongest desire should be know your own
soul. That's literally the gayest thing
I've ever read in my life.
Honestly, is Jason Casper gay?
I don't know.
I don't know. I'll have to ask him. But
here's the thing. Make sure to follow me
on Twitter because you don't want to
miss this juicy goodness over on
Twitter.
Oh man, what a crazy day it is in the
crypto space. What a crazy day it is in
the crypto space, man. We are in
straight chop city. We got to give a big
shout out to everybody in the house. All
right, first of all, big shout out to
the null paradox. Shout out to Ali
Gaming Tube HD. Shout out to Johnny. He
wants to know, is Jason Casper bald?
Is Jason Casper bald?
You tell me. All right, you tell me. Is
Jason Casper bald?
You tell me. How's the hair? How does
the hairline honestly look? All right,
in all seriousness now, yes, I cut my
own hair. Okay, and I was just telling
my wife the other night, you know what?
I should probably get a real haircut
once every three years or so. I get a
professional haircut to fix the damage I
do every takes three years to do the
damage.
But h what do you think? How's the hair?
Wait, hang on now. How's the hair?
Pretty cool, right? Pretty dang cool.
pretty dang cool.
Yeah. Let's see here. Let's let's let's
pop on to the Bitcoin chart and let's
see what's happened.
Um
let's see. Let's go ahead and pull a fib
low to high. Yeah.
Yeah, that's good. We're at the golden
pocket.
Yeah, we're at the golden pocket. Good
place for a quick TP if you're taking a
little bit of a scalp trade here. You
know, a little bit of a scalp trade.
Not the worst place to take a TP,
honestly. You know what I'm saying?
Could we come down lower? Yeah, we
could. We could. We could. Not the worst
place for a quick TP,
you know. Not the worst place for a
quick TP. Alrighty. All right, man.
Let's keep shouting out the dang chat
here [music] as we're starting to get a
little bit of a bounce from this level.
How much do we have on the trade here?
Let's see. We have about [music]
$276,000
on the position. All right. We got about
276K on the trade, baby. All right, so
let's see. Big shout out to Max [music]
Ross. Did I go to Turkey for my hair
transplant?
Um, no, I don't go to Turkey. Shout out
to Shrimplet TV. Now, show the balls.
They probably have more hair. Well, this
is a familyfriendly channel, my friend.
And um Whoa. What did I just do? I just
I just erased myself from the screen.
This is a familyfriendly channel, my
friend. So, yeah, I can't show that. I
apologize. I do apologize. I do
apologize. Let me shrink [music] this
back up here. Got to shrink wrap this
this screen here, man. What a weird I
got I'm going to be honest. This is a
very weird intro to my my stream so far.
Shout out to Margu 3384. Shout out to
Zenad T. He says
he says, "Jesus has a God. Can God have
another God? Well, here's the thing.
Jesus
as [music] a man had a God even though
he is God. Yes, absolutely.
Absolutely. He became a human. He became
a human and as the role of a human, he
has a god. Absolutely 100%.
That's a good question. Shout out to
world seu. He says, "Shea."
Shout out to Baja. Maybe when you have
40, you will lose your hair. when I have
40 40 what bitcoins.
Shout out to Prime Vibes 3.
Shout out to Adam Thomas. [music]
Uh shout out to Senor. Is the hair
getting a little thin? Okay. All right.
But Lee Gaming says, "I'm good." He
says, "I'm good." The real King Salman
says, "Go to a barber."
All right. Uh man, some of these
comments are a little inappropriate.
Jay Casper looking like a white 50 Cent
with a vest on. with the vest on. That's
kind of what I feel like a white 50
Cent. Honestly, when I put on this
Casper Crew hat, I looked at myself in
the mirror and I said, "Is that 50
Cent?" Then I turned on the light and I
said, "Nah." But with the lights off, it
kind of looked like it. When I looked at
that silhouette, you know what I'm
saying? We got a 1 hour Bear Dave.
Absolutely. Trembler 707.
Absolutely. Absolutely 100%.
Um, you took 15,000 steps today on the
treadmill feeling great. That's amazing.
One of the best ways to feel great. I
got an bug bite on my shoulder, man. One
of the best ways to feel great is to
increase your step count.
You know what I'm saying? Shout out to
Jesse Gellick in the chat.
Uh, what's going on, bro? God bless you.
Let's all have a big portion of fries.
What did you see at 64 to enter a trade?
Um, well, I saw that we hit into a naked
point of control [music] as I was
beginning the stream. Uh, we have some
low time frame bearish divergence.
So, money flow coming down on the one
and this was a trade setup that I had
been planning [music] for
uh in the Casper Crew VIP Discord this
morning. Right? So, I was planning for
the short here. This is a pretty key
level, guys. Actually, let's talk about
what's happening now. This is a good
segue into the dang Chisnart.
There's a good segue into the Chisnart.
All right, so let's go ahead and clear
off everything here. Let's go ahead and
clear off everything here.
All right, so here we go. Let's take a
look at what's going on here. Let's
First of all, it's a brand new month,
guys. All right, happy August. Happy
August.
We are closer to the Bitcoin bottom than
we were last month, guys. All right,
once this monthly prints the green dot,
historically, that means that the low is
in. All right, historically, that's what
it means. It means that the low is in.
However, we are still obviously a few
months away from that. And the projected
predicted bottom [music] is going to
happen here. Doesn't mean we're
guaranteed it, but it's probably going
to happen in the middle of October. All
right. So, we're very close. Very close.
Now, when we go to the weekly time
frame, this is where things start to get
a little bit interesting because we had
printed a green dot down here. This
morning, we were printing a red dot, but
so far this weekly candle is looking
pretty dang bullish. All right. It's
looking pretty dang bullish here on the
weekly time frame. Man, I have a bug
bite on my shoulder. Itch is so bad. All
right. Now, on the daily time frame,
look at this. Money flow increasing,
right? green dot about to print, right?
And bullish divergence printed at the
bottom. This next daily green dot does
have the potential, guys, to give us a
pretty juicy squeeze to the upside. It
absolutely does.
Um, but this is the context where we're
in. We we have very bottomy looking
signals
on our monthly, our weekly, [music]
and our daily.
And here's where we're at. And if we go
ahead and we pull the volume across this
entire range going all the way back to
February, you can see that we are back
testing bearishly right now the PC of
the whole range. Okay, back testing
bearishly the PC of the entire range.
What does this mean? Well, honestly
guys, here's what it looks like.
If we can get this green dot printing,
this money flow to me does look pretty
dang bullish. I would not be surprised
if we don't get a move back up to
[music] uh around 68K. This here to me
looks very squeezable. Now, let me just
be very clear. I am not bullish or
bearish right now. I am extremely
neutral. Before I go into any analysis,
let me just tell you where my mind is. I
am extremely neutral. We are at as fair
price as fair price can be. This has
been the fair price of Bitcoin since the
entire beginning of 2026.
All right. Since the entire beginning of
2026, [snorts]
this has been the fair price of Bitcoin
where we are currently at right now. So
[music] to me, that that has to keep me
quite neutral. But I have to recognize
the fact that as we are consolidating
here, when we break this tight chop,
we're going to have significant
follow-through. So pretty much what I'm
looking at now is different targets that
we could have to the upside or to the
downside. And if I see a trade in the
meantime to get into, I'll take the
trade and hold a bit as a runner. Okay,
I'm short right now. I've taken a quick
takerit on the trade, right? Locked in a
little bit of a win. But the thing is, I
do plan to hold the rest of this trade
until potentially zero. All right, same
with the long. I'm in a long right now
from 57ish, whatever K, 59 or whatever
I'm in at 58.4.
All right. I've already guaranteed
$20,000, but I'm ready to hold this
thing to 200,00050 billion quadrillion
point dollars.
Okay. All right. So,
let me just say that before I get into
the analysis. If we are going to start
closing the daily candle now above
$64,000,
why do I think this could be a very
bullish thing and take us up to 68? It's
simply because the oscillator is about
to print a bullish continuation signal.
All right. when you have a bullish
divergence at a major support. Let's not
forget let's just yeah let's let's not
forget the importance of our support
right now. We'll go to the 6 day. We'll
pull a fib from the low to the high and
we are bouncing from the macro 618.
All right, bouncing from the macro 618.
And so this is a very high time frame
major support. We have come into this
support with a very nice looking bullish
divergence. Right? We got ourselves a
juicy cheek on the left, a skinny cheek
on the right. When you have a divergence
like this, the next trigger wave that
you print on the oscillator, especially
especially after a money flow cross,
this gives you a very powerful
continuation of the trend. Right? So, we
would expect that when this green dot
prints here, we would make a higher
high. And that higher high is going to
take us above
67.2.
All right. Now, in addition to this,
when I look and I see this. All right.
This to me looks very squeezable. All
right. This looks very squeezable. We
are consolidating forming a bullish
falling wedge at the PC as the daily
time frame is about to print [music] a
bottom.
That's bullish, man. I'm sorry. That's
pretty dang bullish. All right. Also, we
take a look at the 4 hour time frame and
things are looking pretty bullish here
as well. Look at the 4 hour time frame
right now. Now, I know this only
happened on Bybit. It didn't happen on
other exchanges, but it could easily
happen on other exchanges even if we
come back for the low again, but on
Bybit, we actually already took out this
weekend low and we're we're seeing
bullish divergence on the 4hour time
frame. We're seeing multiple drive of
bullish divergence on the 4 hour, right?
Yes, our target was down to $60,000,
but we're already seeing like really
bullish divergence form here. Okay, so
it's it we had one, two, three drive of
bullish div on the 4 hour. [music]
Again, if it because of all this
bullishness, if we're going to reclaim
the PLC plus this trend line, it would
just make the most sense that we break
out of this wedge and we hit our target.
The technical target of the falling
wedge is going to be
this 67.5ish $68,000 level. Right? Very
just to the top of the range, right?
We're trading a sideways range. Our
clearly defined high is right here. Our
clearly defined low is right here. Okay?
Our clearly defined high is right here.
Our clearly defined low is right here.
And so if our we come down to the low,
we took the low. Now we would expect we
make our way back up to the high to take
the high. All right. Now, if we do
reject from here, because there's a
chance we reject, right? I've taken a
little bit of a short here. I'm not
expecting very much. Okay. If I get
stopped out of this trade right here,
I'm risking what? 400 bucks. I'm risking
4 I'm risking 500 bucks. I'm going to
end up with a small profit. All right.
I've realized on this thing about 1,200
bucks. I'm going to get out of here with
an $800 profit. Worst case scenario, not
a big [music] deal, right? But here's
the thing. If we reject from here, then
I'd say the the highest probability is
that we come down to the value area low
of this macro range around 60,
let's call it, [music] you know, it's a
zone cuz we have many zones of support
here, right? I would say 59K up to
around 61K. This is where we would look
for another long trade. Why would I look
for another long trade if we come down
here? First of all, let's bear in mind
if we do reject from this PC after
holding above like this, right? Keep in
mind we've come up and now we're forming
this pattern, it it's just the highest
probability that we if we're going to
reject from here now that we're going to
come and take all these lows, right? So,
if we're coming back down to this area,
the reason why I would get bullish and
still look for a long trade is is the
same reason why I look for higher from
this area. Right? When we're looking at
the chart on the high [music] time
frames, it really doesn't change. Even
if we drop down to here, every every
single point of data that I've given is
still the same. What what are those
points of data? Well, number one,
bullish divergence at the macro golden
pocket, right? Number two, a bullish
trigger wave with a money flow cross.
[music] Let's say we do drop down here
this week. All right, guess what? We're
still going to have bullish
continuation. We're still going to have
a bullish money flow and we're probably
going to have bullish divergences on
lower time frames as well, right? And
then in this instance, what would we
have? Well, we would have a shoulder
ahead
right here and we would have a shoulder
and then that would give us our higher
low and then yeah, we could shoot for
our higher high up around here. And in
this instance, this would be the next
place to really look for that short
trade to come down for our low. Now,
again, our our low [music] is probably
going to be coming in around October,
right? So, we have plenty of time. This
is the daily time frame here. So, bear
in mind, I know when I'm drawing, I'm
not drawing to scale, but we're talking
like, you know, 60 days, 2 months or so,
right?
So, we have plenty of time in 60 days.
Absolutely. We could see a move to here.
We could see a move up to here. And then
we could see a drop down even lower and
then we could bottom out. Like that is
not too crazy. That is not too crazy.
Right? Every time I talk about this
range, I get the [snorts] weirdest
comments of people saying,
"Not until October, Jason." When I'm
talking about the Bitcoin price pumping
here, they're like, "Not until October,
Jason." Guys, I'm not talking about the
bare market being over. I'm not talking
about the bottom for Bitcoin, right?
>> [music]
>> I'm talking about the near-term price
action as we're leading up to October.
Now, could the bottom be in here? Yeah,
absolutely. Why could the bottom be in?
The reason the bottom could be in is
because on our weekly time frame, even
on our twoe time frame, we have
confirmed bullish divergence. All right,
we have not had confirmed bullish
divergence on our twoe time frame since
the bottom. All right, over here, right
now, we have confirmed. All right, this
is not just printing anymore. This is
confirmed. We are uh we are here in if
we're going to compare the market cipher
B to last [music] time, we are here. All
right, so we're in that range right now.
If we're going to look at like what the
chart looked like last exact bottom, the
bottom had been in already, November
2022. And then the next month in
December, we make a higher low and then
that's it. Okay, so right now the bottom
if things are going to play out like
this with the twoe bull dip, the bottom
is in already in June and now we make a
higher low. We make a higher low
somewhere in here and then boom, we're
out, right? It's very possible. It's
very possible. Now, the reason why I
don't think it's super possible is
because again, we want to respect
[music] the time frame. Now again,
typically we're looking at 360 days, 365
days until that bottom comes in. So you
look historically as the Bitcoin price.
All right.
Yeah, looks like this short trade is is
I might not make it. All right. We might
get stopped out for an $800 profit.
So, you know, typically speaking, all
right, every single time it's it takes
at least a year for the bottom to be in.
And of course, we really start to see
this the last two cycles where really at
365 days is about the exact bottom. You
know, in 2014, h we we did come in a
little bit lower after that. But in
general, that low was in. [music] So,
this is why we're looking at October.
Okay? It's the four-year cycle.
You know, you got to be on a four-year
cycle. All right? You blast gear hard
for four years, a four-year cycle, and
then you just rip rip yourself off it.
No post cycle therapy. zero. All right.
No aromatase inhibitors. [music] All
right. You just blast yourself full of
excess testosterone and random exogenous
compounds for four years straight as
hard as possible and then you just stop
everything cold turkey. That's the
Bitcoin cycle every single time. The
four-year Trump is signing some
executive orders. Huge shout out to our
super chat who said from James who says
is orderflow for for crypto very
valuable to learn. It's valuable to
learn. Absolutely. I mean it tells you
what's happening in the market, right?
It tells you exactly what is happening
live. There's no guessing. There's no
questioning. Um do I use it often to
take trades? I personally don't use it
very often. Do I like to have it? Yes, I
absolutely do. Does it give me extra
confluence if I'm looking for a specific
type of trade setup? Yes. Here's the
thing. [music] There is so much you can
do on Market Monkey.
It goes way beyond even what I know,
right? There's so much you could do
here. There's so many things you could
look at here. It's it is important to
know. Um, but here's something I would
tell every single trader, okay? When it
comes to trading,
what you need to do first is instead
instead of trying to
learn a whole bunch of stuff in the
beginning, what you need to do is
[music]
learn something very very simple. Like I
cannot stress enough how important it is
to just start with the most basic
support and resistance and looking for
some little thing to either tell you to
pull the trigger or not to pull the
trigger and then learning risk
management. All right, if you learn just
some basic analysis and apply risk
management with the most basic strategy,
you are going to be much better off than
people who are looking for that secret
thing that's going to make them
profitable. cuz uh there is no secret
thing to make you profitable. There's no
indicator, there's no order flow,
there's nothing. What it is is having a
riskmanagement strategy in place and
knowing some basic analysis. So you you
understand, okay, this is a resistance.
This is a place to look for a short
trade. I know how much I'm risking. I
know how much I'm trying to get.
Right? And once you have that very
basic, stupidly simple strategy with the
risk management, then you build on top
of it. Then you go deeper and you learn
more. You use more tools and
then you're you're stacking your new
skills on top of the very basic
foundation.
All right? You got to stack the new
skills on top of your basic, stupidly
simple foundation.
If you're chasing that one thing that's
going to change your trading, you're
you're in a losing battle. You're never
going to find that. All right? You're
never going to find that. I promise you.
I promise you.
So, just keep that in mind. Yeah, it's
good to know order flow for sure. All
right. [crying] Uh shout out to James
still again for another super chat.
Don't I usually TP? I usually do, but
when I took this trade,
I told uh the crew that I'm looking for
a very quick takeprofit. All right. I
was I I you know I said I'm looking for
a super quick takeprofit.
So
um let's see. Yeah, let's pop on the
good old Casper Crew VIP Discord at
Jason Caspertrading.com to join the best
trading community in the world. All
right, but you could see here when I
took the trade, I said I've taken a
quick scalp from here, looking for a
fast takeprofit. And then at the golden
pocket, that's when I said time to hit
that TP. And you know, actually that
golden pocket just so happened to be,
you know, the exact bottom so far.
Doesn't mean we can't come lower, but if
we're looking for a scalp trade, you
know, look at this. Yeah. So from that
golden pocket was right here. This is
where I said, "Time for the TP." All
right. And so, yeah, I was looking for a
fast TP. I was looking for a quick
scalp. Nothing more, nothing less. A
quick scalp. Fast TP. All right. In and
out real fast. [music]
All right. And that's exactly what we
done did. All right. That's exactly what
we done. Did. All right. Now, guys, a
quick reminder. Bitbase is giving away
$500 a week.
All you got to do is sign up using my
link. You get VIP level 7 fees, plus
you get
a chance to win $500 [music] every
single week. Guys, I also have to remind
you that Blowin
is giving away $2,000
every single week. All you have to do is
sign up using my link, join my free
Discord, and once you're in the free
Discord, you can figure out how you can
enter a raffle every single week to win
a prize of
$2,000. So, every single week, we're
giving away $2,500. If you're in my VIP
Discord, obviously, we're giving away
way more in there. But, you know, I got
to give a shout today to the winners of
the blow fin challenge.
Um, let's see. Yeah, the blow fin
challenge. Let's see. Let's highlight
our winners. [music] The $2,000 blow fin
giveaway.
Uh, yeah. Who's who [music] who are our
winners? Oh, this is the new one. It
ends in 7 days. Yeah. So, now guys, join
now. You can enter this raffle for the
$2,000 blow fin giveaway
this morning. Archer Lane. Oh, this was
actually last time. When was this? I
don't know.
Anyway, we're giving away $2,000 a week
courtesy of Blow Fin. All right, make
sure to check it out. Make sure to check
it out. All right, check it out. Check
it out if you're interested. If you're
not, it's okay. Shout out to CryptoCrank
in the house. What's going on,
CryptoCank? Did you take a scout from
here? I took a little scout from here,
CryptoCrank, I took a little scout from
here over on Bitbase.
Already locked in a grand, so let's see
what happens. You know, I took a scalp
over on Bitbase, you know, just trying
to lock in some profits.
What am I wearing, Thor? A bulletproof
vest. You laring going to war with the
charts. Yes. Yes. It's a mindset thing.
It's a mindset thing, [music] Thor.
How much is my win rate? Very low. Fame
loops. [music] It's low. All right. I
multiple times on here have chatgpted
my trades, my win rate. We've gone over
it all. In fact, this account here, I
mean, I've only been trading this
account for about a month. All right.
So,
let's see. Taking 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
11 [music] 12 trades.
1 2 3 4 5 six losses. 50% win rate.
Okay. 50% win rate. I'm up I'm up about
50k on the dang month. All right. You
guys have literally seen me do my do my
entire win rate going all the way back
to March on every trade I've taken on
Antarctic Exchange and my win rate is
what? Less than 50% yet I'm up six
figures. So my win rate is low. All
right, my win rate is low. But here's
the thing. That's because of my trading
strategy. All right, it's because of my
trading strategy. I can be profitable
with a low win rate. It's because of the
risk management. It's because of the
invalidations. It's because you're
setting yourself up to make more money
than you're losing over time. All right.
Um,
freestyle.
Yeah, you're right. This is the
freestyle beat, you know. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
All right. Cryptocrank says we're
dumping, baby. Are we shorting?
I'm shorting. I'm short right now. I'm
in a little bit of a short. Okay. Like a
little bit of a short. Well, actually
that's not true. I have I have about
$475,000
on short trades right now.
All right. That's it. That's about it.
Okay. About $475,000 on short trades
right now.
Um when you're getting income from
YouTube and referral links and paid
Discourse, it takes a lot of
psychological pressure. Absolutely. 100%
100%. There, you know. Yeah. I I you're
absolutely right. you know, having a a
business is it takes [music] Yeah, it
takes a lot of the pressure off of
trading.
I always say this and it's it's very
difficult for people to um
to get to this place, but if you cannot
care at all about the money, that's when
the money just starts to come with your
trading because it takes away the
psychological element of feeling like
you need to earn the money, right? It
allows you to stick to the plan better,
right? Yeah, that's 100% true. This is
why I always am a huge proponent of
starting some kind of a business. You
know, trading is one aspect of being
self-sufficient for me. For me, right?
I'm about a well-rounded
self-sufficiency lifestyle. All right?
I'm a homesteader. I grow my own food. I
raise my own animals. I literally live
off-rid right now. This stream is 100%
solar powered. All right. This stream
right now is solar powered. All right.
The sun's behind a cloud, which means
the Tesla walls over here in my garage
are powering this live stream. Okay.
Okay, I'm off grid. I'm not in the water
grid. I'm not in the electric grid. All
right. Um I I for me the the three
pillars of self-sufficiency
is number one. All right. Start
businesses. Like businesses are assets.
People don't realize this. A business is
a literal asset.
All right. It's something that generates
cash flow. It's something that generates
income. Then you take that income and
you do two things with it. You build
infrastructure,
right? So you can produce your own
assets, [music] your own food, your own
water, your own electricity, right? And
then the final layer of that in my
opinion is investing, right? I don't
look at trading as like my ticket out of
the system. I look at trading as an
addition because I'm out of the system,
right? But that's just my own personal
view. You know what I'm saying?
Um,
are four-year cycles subjective? Yes,
everything's subjective. J Gilby,
everything is absolutely subjective,
right? Nothing can be known for certain.
Again, this is why it all goes back to
the risk management and the most, you
know, and just having having some kind
of a strategy. Whenever you make a
trade, whenever you have a bias,
whenever you invest in anything,
you have to do it as if your thesis is
right. Even though you know there's a
chance, your thesis is wrong. [music]
You're taking on that risk, right? And
so this is why every single trade you
take, every single move you make, every
cake you bake, every step you take,
you have to have the plan for what to do
if it goes in your favor, what to do if
it goes against your favor. And by doing
that, you're capping the risk.
You're increasing the reward.
You're making sure you're not taking
yourself out of the game in one stupid
decision.
And over time, doing it that way is
going to allow you to make profits
slowly and steadily. [music] All right.
Slowly and steadily wins the race. All
right. [snorts] Um, [music]
yeah, I do sell chicken milk on the
black market. And let me tell you, it's
hard to milk the hens. All right. It is
hard to milk those hens, baby. Um,
all right. Count
the henny. Count Fenny is short. Okay,
cool. Me, too. I'm in a little short
here. Let's see what happens. Am I not
afraid? We get a 5second 66k candle and
your stop loss gets hit. I'm not afraid.
It might happen, but I'm not afraid. All
right. I'm not afraid.
Um, [music]
is it a bulletproof vest? I guess
there's only one way to really find out,
and I'm not trying to find out. All
right. [music]
Is there a specific reason for the fast
TP? Yeah, there's a specific reason for
the fast TP. All right. If we break this
level, boom, we're going straight up to
$65,000.
All right. Um, and when I look at the
12minut time frame here on market cipher
B. All right. To be blunt, we just got a
money flow cross. All right. The
12minute money flow cross after a
12minute bullish divergence is a
powerful thing. I don't want to be
shorting a 12-minute money flow cross.
Why did I short this? Well, look at the
one minute, guys. You know, the one
minute money flow at the moment of the
trade was crossing from the blue into
the per telling me we have a good scalp
on our hands for a fast TP. All right,
the 5-second money flow, 5-second
strategy gave the signal. All right,
divergence money flow coming out here.
All right, telling me we have a quick
scalp. All right, the six minute here,
the diver, the money flow is getting
getting thicker here. All right, money
flow is getting thicker for me. This is
fast scalp signal. All right. Could we
drop lower? Yeah. Yeah. So, look, I take
a partial. I let the rest ride, man.
You know, I take a partial. I let the
rest ride. What about crystals and tarot
cards? I wouldn't do that stuff. I I You
know what? That would open up doorways
to demonic influences in your life that
will mess with you. You don't want to do
that. And if you do do that, I would
repent of and I would renounce it in
Jesus name. Honestly, I would repent of
that and I would renounce it and and and
ask the Lord to break any kind of
doorway that you may have opened for the
demonic forces to influence you or to
mess with your life, right? Break that.
Break that. You got to break that. It's
some spiritual warfare
slowly is the fastest way to get to your
destination. Amen, Trader Gio. We know,
bro. We know, man.
Yeah. [music]
And sometimes it happens quick with
those big trades, but you got to be
careful with those big trades because
they mess with your mind sometimes. You
know what I'm saying? Um,
but yeah, we got the vest on today,
guys. Look, I'm trying to get back into
the weighted vest mindset. You know what
I'm saying? Seven figure positions,
weighted vest, Casper crew hat, and
underneath this, I got my market cipher
shirt on. You know what I'm saying?
Where do I live? I live off-rid. You
know what I'm saying? Do the Tesla
batteries emit radiation? Probably, bro.
Probably.
You know what? Probably.
My poll's confusing. I know. I know.
That's a little bit on purpose. It's
kind of like a joke.
Yeah, probably. They admit radiation.
Everything emits radiation. You know
what I'm saying? I've got Wi-Fi in the
house, radiation. I've got cell phones
in the house, radiation. I've got LED
lights in the house because they use
less electricity. Radiation.
You can't even go outside, honestly,
without the the the the the satellites
beaming down radiation. You know what
I'm saying?
Yeah, of course they probably give
radiation.
Everything is radiation these days. You
know what I'm saying? So, you got to you
got to pick your battles. And for me,
honestly, I'd rather live off-rid nice
and comfortably here with some radiation
than uh really rough it out here with no
radiation. You know, risk versus reward
for me, you know.
For me, I'll just be honest, you know, I
try I tried to I tried to toughen myself
up, but there was, you know, when me and
my wife first got married, we were in we
were in the mentality, you know, we were
we were we didn't use air conditioning
in the summertime, and a lot of times we
don't now even, but we do have it in
parts of our house, right? But, you
know, we're trying to build up our
toughness. But the thing is, sadly, I
didn't grow up Amish. I wish I did. I
wish I grew up Amish, but I don't really
have those kind of life skills. So, for
me, you know what? have little of some
modern conveniences with with the
radiation so I can trade Bitcoin on the
treadmill.
You know what I'm saying?
How do I deal with the Christian
non-gambling sin with your trading? I
stress I
uh non-gambling sin. I don't know. Is
gambling a sin? I don't know. Can you
show me a Bible verse that says
gambling's a sin? If you can, I'll stop
trading right now. But here's another
thing. what I'm doing is not gambling,
right? There's a big difference between
trading and gambling. There's a huge
difference between trading and gambling.
Do you know what I mean? If you are
gambling, that could be a sin [music]
because you're not being a good steward.
You're not taking care of your family.
You're throwing away money that should
be used to support you and your family.
Okay?
But what I'm doing is not gambling.
Okay? What I'm doing is definitely not
gambling. All right. It's it's this is a
business. All right. Trading is a
business if you're doing it properly,
right?
So
that's my view on it. All right.
But you [music] know what? The Bible
actually does say something about
investing.
All right,
let's see. The parable of the 10
virgins, right? The parable of the 10
virgins,
right? This is where it's a parable to
tell you that if God gives you
something, you have to use it for him.
Right? And don't keep it to yourself.
Right?
So in the instance of the person who
received one talent, he buried it in the
ground. He didn't do anything with it.
And God got mad at him and said, "You
should have invested
my money. That way I would have received
interest."
[music] Right?
So in this parable, which is a parable,
right? [music]
The Lord is saying, "You know what? I
gave I gave you this money. You should
have at least invested it so I would
have had a little something extra when I
came back.
So maybe maybe trading is biblical. You
know what I'm saying? Maybe trading is
biblical.
I don't know. You know,
um,
I'm a well- paid decision maker and a
professional loser. That's what trading
is. Yeah, I guess that's true. I guess
that's true. I do consider myself that.
Honestly, I am nothing but a burnout.
Like in reality, I mean, I I I I sew the
seeds of uh being a burnout, but the
Lord has been very merciful and gracious
unto me. You know what I'm saying?
[music] You know, yeah, trading's
biblical. You heard it here first. The
truth is, we are the Anunnaki.
Nah, we're not the Anunnaki, silly
goose.
Well, maybe you are. I'm not. All right.
Do I have videos on risk management?
Absolutely.
You know, absolutely. I got videos on
risk management. In fact, you know,
let's uh let's take a look at the Jason
Casper YouTube channel real quick. All
right. Go to the Jason Casper YouTube
channel. Go to playlists.
All right. Go to playlists and go to the
Jason Casper free
>> trading course. Go to session number
two, how to use risk management to be
profitable. In fact, check out this
18-part free trading course, absolutely
free, free.99, where myself, Jason
Casper,
I mean, how would you not trust this guy
right here? Look at that. This is the
most trustworthy look I've ever seen in
my life. My goodness.
[laughter]
Oh, it's weird. Yeah. And and I do have
the course. I do have the orderflow one,
too. If you want to learn orderflow, you
can learn it from me. Yours truly. All
right. Who wouldn't trust this guy? Who
wouldn't trust this guy? You know what
I'm saying?
All right, let's see. Crypto crank, are
you still short, man? Are you still
short?
Do I prefer going short or long? I don't
know. It It really depends. I can't
know, you know.
I can't know.
I can't give an answer.
Am I a flatearther? I don't [music]
know. I don't know.
When was my first big win that changed
everything?
It's hard to say that, Mr. Jinx, because
honestly,
uh, well, I'd have to say my first
actual big win in crypto that changed
everything had nothing to do with
leverage trading. It had to do with
buying Bitcoin on spot in 2016
where, you know, I turned a couple I
turned tens of thousands into hundreds
of thousands. All right,
that was life-changing cuz I was able to
buy this off-rid homestead. [music]
That was life-changing.
All right. Um,
after that, there has never been a big
win that was lifechanging. Uh, but I
would say this. So the last bare bull
cycle, so from 2021 until 2025,
I was really locked in during that time.
And during that time,
there's not one single trade I took.
There's not one single investment I
made, but from my spot and my leverage
trading, I was able to
make a lot of money. All right? So, and
it's life-changing in a sense that if if
just let's just say for example, okay,
the economy doesn't crash and the dollar
doesn't die and there's not a war or
something which all these things could
very, you know, as long as the fecal
matter doesn't come into contact with
the revolving apparatus and things go on
with some sort of normal,
you know, society like they've been for
the past 30 years of my life, then
technically I don't have to work ever
again, right? Technically, like to
support my family, I mean, right? I'm I
I'm I'm retired, you could say. [music]
Okay. I could retire.
All right. I don't have to have a job
ever. [music] All right. Now, I say that
understanding that life is very
unpredictable and anything could happen
and nothing's secure, right? So, I it's
not like I'm it's not like I'm living
with the mindset that I'm retired. I'm
going to do nothing. You know what I'm
saying? But that's life-changing in the
sense that you know if for example I
ever wanted to just disappear
and you know go live somewhere totally
random and have no cell phone. I could
right
I could
for now.
Tartaria [music]
we're talking about flat earth. We're
talking about Tartaria.
Uh is today this is the month we're
supposed to lose gravity, lose gravity.
Meltology and Tartaria. Yeah, like the
whole earth melted.
You know, this gu some some crazy
theories. You know, the um Satan's
little season theory,
you know, some different escatological
views and
whole bunch of crazy stuff, man. If you
go long and short, you can't lose. You
know what? Shout out to Bon Voyage. God
bless you. Thank you so much for being
here. Shout out to steak sauce. What's
with all the props? Plunger. Chicken
glasses. Pirate wig hat. You know what?
I haven't used props in a while, but I
do have the plunger still. But I got a
little hungry. I got a little hungry
with the plunger. You know what I mean?
Ain't no money like short money.
Um,
gravity is a myth. Maybe it's just
density and buoyancy, right? Maybe it
maybe it is. I don't know. Maybe the
whole universe is electromagnetic. I
don't know. You know, I'm not a
scientist, you know.
I'm not a scientist. Oh, yeah. Okay.
It's magnetism. This guy Johnny, he
says, "You know what? The big G, the big
G, it's really just electromagnetism."
You know, everything else is
electromagnetic. We are, you know what
I'm saying?
But
yeah, I know, right, Senor? But look,
it's it's the chat provokes me to these
topics, bro. I wouldn't be talking about
the flat earth and Tartar and
esquetology, but the chat's bringing it
up. I'm trying to keep it on crypto,
man,
you know. I'm trying to keep it on
crypto. Um,
how do you calculate a stop-loss? Very
simple. All right. Mindset Titan. Very
simple. Here's what you do. Actually,
there might even be a free tool for it.
Let me see if if like this might
actually even
calculate it for you.
If you um double click this tool [music]
um let's say you want to risk
1%
[music]
uh
yeah this this will probably tell it for
you if you're going by lot size and I
don't know how to calculate that into
dollar size or I don't know what that
means. Here's the formula. All right,
check out the check out the free course
and go to session number two. All right,
but the formula basically is your the
amount risked divided by your stop-loss
percent. All right, so the actual
formula is going to be the amount of
dollars that you're risking and you're
going to divide that by your percent
stop-loss.
All right, so if you have $100 [music]
in your account and you want to risk 1%,
you're going to do $1. That's how much
you want to risk. You're going to divide
that by, let's say you have a,
you know, a 1% stop loss, right? We're
going to keep this as simple as
possible. All right, that what you're
going to do is you're going to divide
one by 0.01.
All right, so 1 / [music] 0.01,
that's going to give you 100, right?
Divided by 0.01 equals 100. And that's
the amount of dollars you put on your
trade. All right? Now, if you want to
have a let's say a 3% stop loss right
now, you do 1
/ 0.03 and now you have $33.33
that you're putting on the trade, right?
I guess you ask me how to calculate a
stop-loss, not a This is how you
calculate a position size based on your
stop-loss. The way you calculate a
stop-loss is basically you're just
saying where should the stop loss be,
right? So, for example, this trade I'm
in now, where should the stop loss be?
The stop loss should be above the high,
right? The stop loss should be above the
high. Okay? So, in this instance, we
have a 0.02%
stop loss, right? So, if you have $100
in your account, $100 divided by 0.002.
That means you could put basically
$50,000 on the trade and be risking your
$100.
Isn't that crazy? Isn't that crazy?
So,
I'm sorry. No, not not $50,000. 1
divided by 0.002.
$500. There you go. You can put $500 on
the trade. If you're trading with $100,
we're trading with $100. We're not
risking $100. I did the formula for if I
was risking $100. That' be if you were
risking your whole account. You put 50
grand on the trade. Whoops. No. So you
have, you know,
that's how you calculate your stop loss.
You just say, where should it go? Where
are you wrong? Like if this is if this
is really a rejection from the naked
monthly point of control, where am I
wrong? I'm wrong if we make a higher
high.
And we might come up to 64K and reject.
That's fine. All right. That's fine.
That's fine. That's fine. That's fine.
>> [music]
>> Um,
yeah, we got some crazy stuff in the
chat. Do gays go to heaven? That's some
crazy stuff in the chat. Look, sinners
don't go to heaven no matter what. If
you're gay or straight. All right, but
here's here's the here's the gospel
here. Here here's what here's what the
good news is. All right, man is
separated from God because of sin. But
God desiring relationship and
restoration,
God himself became flesh. God entered
into his own creation. He was born
through a virgin woman. He lived a
sinless life. He died on the cross. His
perfect life, his death paid for the sin
that humanity committed. So God can
justly forgive humanity for the sins
that we have committed. He didn't stay
dead. Three days later, he rose from the
dead as a representative of humanity. He
ascended to the right hand of the father
as a representative of humanity. And so
now he promises if we put our faith in
him and what he did paying for our sin
and as a representative being reunited
to God.
If we repent which means we purpose in
our heart and we purpose in our mind.
Right now the behaviors I'm doing are
leading to my destruction. I don't
desire to do these anymore. I desire to
walk in God's ways. He promises to fill
you with his Holy Spirit and cause you
to become a born again new creation. All
right? A fundamentally new creation with
a new birth, a new spiritual birth where
you're no longer on the trajectory to
destruction, but you are on the
trajectory to eternal life. where you
get to exist in the state that God
originally created humanity to live in
without death, without separation,
without broken relationships,
perfect unity with God.
And so, as a born again new creation,
it doesn't matter what things you have
struggled with in the past. Doesn't
matter what things you struggle with
now. If you're truly a born again new
creation, you are being changed and
there will be evidence of that change in
your life.
And so, yeah, if you were gay and now
you're a born again new creation, guess
what? You're going to heaven. And if you
were straight and now you're a born
again new creation, guess what? You go
to heaven. If you're straight and you're
not a born again new creation, sorry,
right? And if you're gay and you're not
a born again new creation, I'm sorry.
According to scripture,
you're headed for destruction. You need
to be born again. That's the only hope
for humanity. Period.
Right? That's that's that's the only
hope for humanity. There there's the
human condition is that life is short,
hard, full of pain, and then it's over.
But God created humanity with eternity
written on our hearts. We we know that
there's more than this. But the only way
to actually experience the more than
this is through Jesus. That's it. Let's
get the music back on.
And actually, let's go pee in the
bushes.
Let's go pee in the bushes.
>> All right. [singing and music]
>> We're going to go take a pee in the
bushes, baby.
Um,
let's pee in the bushes,
man.
How much capital would someone
realistically need in order to live off
of trading? Making 6 to 10K a month? Um,
well, it really does depend on your Ooh,
a locust.
There's a [music] locust in this bush.
It's locust season. It depends on your
It depends on your trading style. Okay.
So if you are a swing trader,
you know, it depends on the market
condition, but I'd say it is possible to
make that with, you know, let's say
hundred $100,000.
Um, you know, that's that's I'd say
that's that's pretty reasonable. If you
are
more of a day trader, could be a little
bit less for me. the way I've traded
historically and the sweet spot for me,
[music] let's say making like four to
sixk, not six to 10k, making four to 6K
in a very relaxed state would be like
between 150 and $250,000. [music] I'm
talking about a very relaxed state. The
one thing you don't want to do is put
yourself in a position where you feel
like you need to take a trade in order
to make the money, [music] right? If
we're being very selective and very
spoiled about our trades, trading my
style that I like to trade, 150K to 200K
a month is the sweet spot.
Man, you know what? Looks like my
laptop's freaking out from the heat. I
might have to take this into the into
the basement gym and let this laptop
cool down real quick here. you know,
um,
Crypto Crank says for scalping, $50 to
$100,000 is the key. I mean, honestly,
yeah, it's funny cuz he said for
scalping, but I I feel like that's kind
of true for swing trading, too, because
if you get in that one good trade, you
know, that one could easily make you,
you know,
tons of stuff.
Um,
man, I I don't know what's going on
right now with this uh
this computer here is freaking out. Do
you guys even hear what I'm saying right
now? Can you guys hear what I'm saying?
I ain't playing. Can you hear what I'm
saying? Put a one in the chat if you can
even hear me.
Um,
ex civilians is his love for humans is
equal to his disdain. Yeah, humanity is
really messed up, you know. That's
that's why that's why we need the good
news of Jesus the Messiah. That's the
only way to fix humanity.
Um,
all right. Cryptocrank says you can use
50 to 100K with zero leverage and make
60 tok 10K easily. Yeah, if you're like
a really good trader. Like that's the
thing. Like, so
if you're if you're a spot-on trader.
All right, people can hear me. People
can hear me. Dang. So, what's up with my
music?
See here. Let's take a look.
I guess my music closed out, right? Huh?
Is this This was my old stream.
H
see here. Let's go to playlists here.
Let's go to the uh this and uh let's go
to this here. Yeah, here we go. This is
the music I like.
Oh, looks like uh there we go.
>> [snorts]
>> Wait,
looks like the issues on my end, not
your end.
Yeah, issues on my end, not your end.
There we go. There we go. There we go.
All right. Bitcoin's back to dumping,
baby.
Pee on the laptop.
Okay. [music]
All right. All right.
50K to $100,000 is wide range.
Honestly, the only way to really know
that answer is to is to start trading
yourself and figure out what kind of a
trader you are and how trading fits in
your lifestyle.
That's the only way to really know that
answer for yourself, you know. All
right. Sorry guys for all the craziness
here. All right. [music] Sorry for all
the craziness here.
Yeah, I'm so sorry for all the
craziness.
Yeah. Uh, Tuli Manu, I totally agree
with you, my friend. Actually, I I 100%
agree with you, but I uh here's the
thing. I have to communicate in a way
that uh
people understand. All right, [music] my
friend. So, if someone asks
if someone asks me, would I go to heaven
if [music] All right. What do you think
is a a more spiritually mature response
to give that person? Should I sit there
and explain? We're not really going to
go to heaven.
God's going to make a new earth.
And this whole idea of heaven is like,
you know, that's not really biblical.
We're, you know, it's a physical, bodily
resurrection. We're going to live in a
new earth. And maybe we'll be able to go
to heaven, but we can't really know
everything perfectly.
Or would I just tell them really, what
are they asking? They're asking
They're asking, "What can I do to be
saved, my friend?
So, what am I going to do? Am I going to
talk to them about how maybe their
concept of heaven might not be 100%
biblical? Or am I going to share the
gospel with them, bro? What What What
would you rather do in that situation?
You know what? Who cares if we go to
heaven or if we go to the new earth? I
don't know what's going to happen after
this earth is gone. But Jesus knows
what's going to happen. So, I don't
really care as much what people believe
about what happens, where they're going
to be, as much as I care about if people
know the only way that they could
actually get to experience that, my
friend. Do you know what I'm saying,
bro?
You get what I'm saying?
Um,
Earth is flat. Why we got so many flat
earthers in the chat? You know, we got a
lot of flat earthers in the chat, you
know.
Come on, guys. If the earth was flat,
would you be able to go to the beach and
see the ships go off over the curvature?
You know,
you know, um, if you're a funded trader,
you don't even need capital. That's true
as well. That's true as well.
Most importantly, if a turtle loses his
shell, is he naked or homeless? Well,
here's the thing. I [music] had a pet
turtle once. His name was Jonathan the
Turtle.
And we actually gave him, believe it or
not, clothes to wear, special turtle
clothes. [music] And these special
turtle clothes allowed him to be
homeless yet not naked when he lost his
shelf. So, I'd say it depends on the
turtle. Okay.
Can I speak on the book of Enoch?
Yeah, I think Enoch's a great book to
read. Go read it. All right.
Wow. We're dropping now. Oh my goodness.
Oh my goodness.
We're dropping now.
>> What do you want to know about the book
of Enoch? What do you want to know about
the book of Enoch?
[music]
You know, what do you want to know about
the book of Enoch?
Yeah, it makes [music] sense, right?
>> [singing]
>> Shout out to Auggie. Happy Monday, Jay.
How's the fam? How are you? And how's
the farm? Everyone is great, you know.
Praise the Lord. Praise God. You know,
praise Jesus. What can I say? Praise the
Lord. I'm so thankful. I'm full of
gratitude. I'm full [snorts] of
gratitude. You know, praise the Lord.
Um,
you know, I really am full of gratitude.
What's my TP in the short? Well, [music]
the TP in the short was right here. All
right. This is the TP1 in the short.
Now, I'm just going to hold this in case
of massive dumperoni. All right. So,
let's see. Let's see what's going to
happen here. All right, here we go.
You know,
[music]
>> but I'm just messing with you, Johnny
Asha. Trust me, you must be new to this
channel, bro. [music]
I was using I was just joking about the
ships going over the horizon thing.
Yeah. All right. So, let's let's see
like where do we expect this to go next
would be basically [music]
uh taking out the lows of this mini
range here. So, really the next target
for this short trade is going to be
right here. Right. Trade the range. Next
target is going to be here. But we
haven't even [music] lost the first low
yet after the rejection. So really, this
would be our our next target here. All
right, this would be our next target
right down here. But man, we're getting
an aggressive bounce. Oh my goodness,
the bulls are back in town. The bulls
are back in town.
You know,
uh, Seenor, I don't think they
necessarily knocked the Book of Enoch
out of the cannon, bro. Like, uh, the
Book of Enoch, it was never it was never
really considered
canonical in that way. Okay, it was
never considered on that level by the
Jews. It it was [music] it was
considered on that level by some
Christians. Okay, it was but it was
never widely agreed upon. But here's the
thing. The concept of the biblical
cannon as we think of it today did
[music] not exist in the first century,
right? It really did not exist. You had
a library full of books. Nobody took a
whole bunch of books together and put
them in one big book because they didn't
have books like that, right? They had a
whole bunch of scrolls.
And so
these books could be considered on
different levels, right? It doesn't mean
a book's not true,
if it's not necessarily on the same
level as Moses, so to speak, right?
But um nobody ever like took it out of
it's not like there was a cannon of
books and people took books out, right?
[music]
It was more so as time went on people
agreed which books should be in, right?
There were zero books in and over time
people agreed which books should be in
but nobody ever necessarily took books
out
so to speak.
But
um [music]
I don't I don't necessarily see why it
matters really one way or another. If a
book is valuable to give you historical
and/or spiritual
uh edification, then go ahead and read
that book, right? Whether or not it's in
a book full of other books or not, you
know what I mean?
Whether or not it's in a book full of
other books or not,
you know?
Would
Catholics beg to differ? Catholics, Do
Catholics believe there was a cannon, an
a an official cannon that existed in the
days of uh
the apostles. Does anyone believe that?
I don't know.
Was there a group of books that was
called the official canonical set of
books? I don't I really don't think so.
Sure.
Um,
advice on homesteading. Is it better to
hire a private teacher or do Oh,
homeschooling?
I think it depends, Spicy Noodle, on the
situation because here's the thing. You
know, my wife was a public school
teacher for seven years uh before she
began to homeschool our children. And um
I think it really depends on a lot of
things. Depends on the kids. Some kids
learn better from not their parents. Uh
some kids learn better from their
parents. You could do a combination. You
could do co-ops. You know, you could get
together with uh people, like-minded
people that are all homeschooling their
kids. Uh hiring a private teacher sounds
kind of expensive and probably a little
little unnecessary for most, but if you
can swing it and you trust the teacher,
here's the here's the most important
thing about homeschooling your kids.
You're homeschooling your kids so that
you are uh in control of what they are
learning and and and the worldview that
they develop, right? That's why you're
doing it. And so if you're going to hire
somebody else, make sure that that
somebody else is on the same page as you
ideologically. Otherwise, what's the
point? You know, um
you know what I'm saying?
In the past cycles, we're making highs
in the stock market, but lows in
Bitcoin. I haven't watched or traded in
a good while. I can't get the hang of
it. Well, James, this is a good time to
get into Bitcoin because honestly,
pretty soon, in my opinion, I think that
we are going to see a bull market. So,
you know, I could be wrong, but I'm
really hoping that we do. I'm really
hoping that we do, you know.
Um,
you know,
Any
advice for energy reset, life reset,
getting rid of bad energy?
Um, yeah. I mean, first of all, put your
faith in the Lord Jesus, who is God,
took on humanity
so that we could enter into a
relationship with God. All health begins
spiritually.
And then after that, get your diet
together, get your sleep together.
I think those are some good things to
do.
You know, I know for me, my um
[music]
for me, my diet and my lifestyle
contribute very much so to my high
energy,
right? I feel good. that I have high
energy. I'm I'm I'm very active, you
know, it I I I contribute it first of
all spiritually, right? Second of all,
you got to you got to fuel your body
properly. You got to move your body
properly, right? Diet and exercise.
Do I still think we make a new low? Um
what do you mean like uh a macro low? I
think it's very possible. I I did give
my entire outlook, you know, at the
beginning of the stream where you could
make the argument that the low is in
based on the confirmed twoe bullish
divergence.
All right, but
um [music]
you could also make the case that based
on the four-year cycle, we don't bottom
out until October. And I would prefer
another low. I would prefer another low.
Yeah, I stream on a laptop.
You know,
I stream on a laptop
and you know what? I'm I'm a ve I like I
like to keep things uh very like
unprofessional. I don't know what else
to say. I could never imagine myself on
a desktop, you know? I like to be able
to think that wherever I go, I could
take my office with me. My my trading
office is literally [music]
a laptop and two phones or a phone and
an iPad. Like that's my three monitors.
All right, that's that's my trading
setup. I like to be able to do it in the
car. You know,
I could do it in a box. I could do it
with a fox. I could do it here or there.
I could do it anywhere. You know,
I could do it anywhere.
You know, sailor sold 1,600 Bitcoin
today. Really? I did not hear that. I
did not hear that.
You know,
shout out to bullish on parade
in the chat. Let's see what's going to
happen here.
Why aren't we enjoying Cuba,
CryptoCrank? That's a good question,
bro.
>> [music]
>> It's because um
cuz it's summer, man. You know, it's
summer.
Don't worry. When it's cold, when it's
cold,
then I'll be back in Cuba. I'll be back
in Cuba. Big shout out to Cryptocrank,
guys. Make sure to
make sure to go subscribe to
CryptoCrank. All right.
How do you control your mind?
Well, honestly,
prayer,
fasting,
and just, you know, being obsessed with
seeking the [music] Lord. That's the
that's that's how you got to do it,
honestly.
And it's not going to happen overnight.
It's not going to happen overnight.
Have I traded hype recently? No. Haven't
traded hype recently. I've pretty much
only been trading Bitcoin, you know.
Let's check out Space X real quick. All
right,
let's check out SpaceX
because this thing took a tumble.
Let's see.
Back inside the wedge.
Higher, lower, lower, low. Lower low.
Hm. Let's put on market cipher.
Some bull div on the four.
Double drive.
I don't know.
I do think eventually SpaceX will pump
just because it's SpaceX.
But yeah, look at that thing. I thought
we were going to start to squeeze. I do
think I really do think that we are
going to squeeze. I still think we can
squeeze this, guys. I really do. [music]
I really think we can squeeze it.
The Cubans were partying hard in
Louisville the other day. Oh, some good
food. Yeah, for sure. I do enjoy Cuban
food so much. Honestly,
>> do I make more money on trading or
affiliates? Well, it depends on the
month,
right? I [music] So, like I haven't
taken very many trades.
certain months, January, February or red
months for me in my trading. You know,
if it's a red month in trading,
then I make more on my everything else
is leverage [music]
is to leverage the weak is to control
the masses.
Okay. Okay. [music] Yeah, it's probably
super hot in Cuba right now.
Space X is dead. Looks pretty dead at
some point. I feel like it's got a pump,
you know. At some point, I feel like
it's got to take a pump.
All right, Bitcoin's taking a dump.
Let's see if we can't hit the tar. Come
on, Bitcoin. Come and hit our tar. Guys,
quick reminder. All right, Bitbase
giving away $500 a week. Blow fin giving
away $2,000 a week.
Also, guys, I'm partnered with client
funding. I have a 15% discount on these
accounts if you're interested. All
right. And if you want to join the
Casper crew, you can go to
jasonaspertrading.com. Join the
community where this short scalp was
given in the moment.
All right.
Is Avac good to buy? Look,
you know, I got to be honest with you.
I've got to be honest with you.
I don't know objectively speaking if
we're going to go based on the chart.
Yeah. Like if we're going to be
objective
like look at this thing,
right?
Look at this thing. I mean it's it's
it's
we're buying low. Objectively speaking
from the all-time high at this exact
moment, we are buying at a 95% discount.
If Avac has a future, it's a good thing
to buy. The question you need to answer
is, does AVAX have a future? I can't
answer that for you. I honestly don't
know. My gut feeling is yes.
My gut feeling is yes. Okay. My gut
feeling is that we are going to see
altcoins come back. And even if this
thing doesn't make a new all-time high,
I mean, even if this thing just comes
back up to like the support resistance
flip, it's a 200% gain,
you know?
Man, I have a bug bite on my shoulder
that's acting up again. I got to itch it
with the plunger.
Am I going to smoke some Cubans next
time Cuba? Absolutely.
Absolutely. Yeah, I'll smoke some
Cubans.
Crypto crank says he's passing on the
vax. Avac that is.
Have I heard of the Bible project? I
have not, but it sounds cool. I would
love to check it out.
So, look, Crypto Crank says no. All
right. Jason Casper says yes. You
probably listen to Crypto Crank. All
right.
Do I know anything about Circle? I
don't. But I hope it's I hope
everything's okay because I do hold a
lot of USDC,
you know.
Did I look at the Micro Strategy with
the volume range
volume profile?
Visible range volume profile. No, I
didn't. Let's check out Micro Strategy
with the visible range volume profile.
Right,
let's clear off our analysis here.
Now, just to be honest, I don't plan on
buying any AVAC. I hold all the AVAX I
want. I hold a lot of AVAX. Like, I do,
but I'm I'm pretty much not buying any
alts this time [music] around. I'm only
buying Bitcoin.
Let me make that clear. I I'm only
What's the visible range that we're
looking at here, man?
What time frame are we looking?
[music]
Oh, I mean, most of the volume is all
the way down at $20.
[music] Most of the volume is down
pretty low.
Is that what you're looking at?
We've just come back inside the global
volume value area.
We are bouncing from a low volume node
right here.
We got another low volume node at 54.
That would that would be a nice low at
54. [music] Another low volume node at
40. PC at 29.
Can Avac put in a lower high and make
200%? Absolutely.
But he likes to I'll take my 200% on
Ether Soul, says Crypto Crank. [music]
Open USD is taking over circle. Dang.
Should I get out of USDC?
Shout out to [music] a beer.
Big shout out to a beer in the house.
What does 2B market cap mean? It means
two billion.
two billion dollars in the asset.
Watch as Bitcoin underperforms and alts
out overperform. Yeah. Yeah. Let's see
if that happened. Let's see if that
happens. You know, very well could. Very
well could. I'm still only buying
Bitcoin. Hang on. I'm going to take off
this vest.
You know, you got to be careful with the
weighted vest. I'll tell you one thing,
the weighted vest,
the weighted vest [music] is a secret
weapon.
If you guys like to eat, you know, 7 800
grams of carbohydrates a day and have a
six-pack,
the weighted vest is the ultimate weapon
for achieving that reality. But I'll
tell you, it's a very
delicate tool because if you overdo it,
then it will impede your workout
recovery [music] and then the next thing
you know, you're missing reps
and that means you're going too hard.
So, I I've been very careful with the
weighted vest. try not to get more than
like six, 7,000 steps max with the
weighted vest [music] because right now
I have a really good balance. I'm really
strong in the gym. I'm hitting PRs left
and right.
I'm lean. I'm energetic. I feel good.
I've got the balance right now. I'm I'm
in the groove, you know. Praise the
Lord. I'm I'm in the groove. [music] I'm
on my body. I I I I've got I've got the
uh the equilibrium, [music] the energy
in, the energy out, feeling good, being
lean, being strong.
But if I overdo it with the weighted
vest, [music] that balance is easily
broken.
Low carb diets always deliver. They do.
They will deliver low testosterone, low
energy, low strength, depression. They
will absolutely deliver. High carb diets
will deliver you that strength, that
power, [music] that good mood, that low
cortisol, that high testosterone, that
high libido, that feeling that you just
feel like you're ready to take on the
dang world, and you're always stoked on
life and ready to go get it. That's what
high carbohydrates will do, you know?
That's what low carb That's That's what
high carbs will do, baby. You know, high
carbs, baby, all the way. They call me
high carb J. They call me HDJ.
You know what I'm saying?
No vest needed. Yeah, that's cool. Well,
yeah. Low calories. Exactly. So, the the
weighted vest is the trick for high
calories. All right. Cuz I'm a high
calorie guy. All right. I'm eating about
5,000 calories a day right now.
About 5,000 a day. About 5,100 when it
all averages out. All right. On days
that I don't train, it usually ends up
being around 4,500. On days I do train,
can be up 5,600.
All right. I just eat to satiety. I I I
I I don't limit, but I track cuz I want
to know. I want to know what am I
eating, what am I doing, all this stuff.
I track it. You know, look, I'm a
trader. I'm all about information. You
know, I'm all about charts. I'm all
about charts. You know, you know, I know
my weight every day for the last like
seven years. I know how many calories
I've eaten every day for like the last
nine [music] years. You know, I have
every single lift I've ever done in the
gym for the last like 10 years. Have it
all tracked. You know what I'm saying?
Got it all tracked.
What kind of carbs?
Shout out to Nike Boy Crypto. What
exchange would you use to trade from the
USA between Antarctic and KSEX? Uh
definitely Antarctic because KSEX is a
centralized exchange, man. And and and
yeah, I always would if I had to choose
only one, it would be the DEX for sure.
It would be the DEX. Look, these
centralized exchanges, they're good.
They're convenient. They have low fees,
but you never know when they go bye-bye,
right?
But thank you so much for the super
chat, bro. I appreciate it. You know, um
[music]
some some crazy needy calories.
Yeah, if you train hard, you need
calories. Yeah. Um
have I heard of Sue Becker's bread?
Nope. Have never heard of it. What kind
of carbs do I eat? I eat fruit and
vegetables.
I eat lots of potatoes. Lots of fruit.
Lots of vegetables. lots of potatoes.
I eat
>> [music]
>> uh then on top of that, that's like the
main those main three things is fruits,
vegetables, and potatoes. And then I
will eat buckwheat,
quinoa, and popcorn. Buckwheat, quinoa,
and popcorn.
And then if I'm going to have wheat, it
has to be a real sourdough bread.
preferably an e corn sourdough where
it's just organic iron corn flour,
water, and salt fermented the
oldfashioned way. And then I get carbs
also from dairy. That's it. Uh that's
it. So pretty much just fruits,
vegetables, potatoes, uh popcorn is the
only actual grain I eat.
Uh I'll eat some oatmeal, too. But in
general, it's buckwheat, quinoa.
buckwheat and quinoa, potatoes, fruits,
and vegetables. That's pretty much it.
And then, yeah, a little bit of maybe
eorn wheat or some or some if it's if
it's regular wheat, sourdough, I could
eat that, too. Um, and then some oatmeal
sometimes. That's about it.
Those are the carbs. And then dairy has
carbs. You know what I'm saying?
Dairy has carbs. So, you know, Greek
yogurt has carbohydrates in it. I get
Greek yogurt from the local farm. Full
fat Greek yogurt. Man, it tastes so dang
good. I'll tell you. But it does have
some sugar in it, right? Some lactose.
Some lactose. You know what I'm saying?
Um,
Adam Thomas, like, I don't know, man. I
really don't know. So, I I I I have to
talk to them about it cuz like what the
heck, honestly.
Uh, what's up? Yeah, High Carb J. That's
what they call me. High carb J.
No rice. No, I don't like rice at all.
Rice is for skinny guys that have
trouble gaining weight. Rice has like no
nutrition in it. It's literally you
might as well just eat sugar. You might
as well just eat sugar. I mean, it's
just like carbohydrate for the sake of
carb. It's for those weird hard gainers.
I don't understand you hardgain gainers
out there. All right. I'm I'm morbidly
obese. All right. I have I have morbidly
obese genetics. I could eat forever. I'm
always hungry. Always. Even if I do
nothing. I was super obese as like a
teenager, right? Probably like 40% body
fat. I'm not even kidding. I was like
massive, right? [snorts]
Rice, what a waste. You might as well I
It doesn't fill you up at all. It
doesn't have any minerals, vitamins.
Probably has arsenic in it. Now, don't
get me wrong, I love rice. It tastes
great. I love it. As a fat guy, I love
rice, man. Give me some Chinese food
with the sticky rice. You know what I'm
saying?
Put some sweet and sour sauce on it or
or even just plain the sticky rice. I
love it. I love rice. But I could eat
like, you know, literally I could eat
two cups of dry rice in one sitting and
still be hungry. Like, so no, I don't
eat rice. It's not worth it for me. It's
not worth for me. If I'm going to eat a
carbohydrate, it has to have lots of
micronutrients, minerals, potassium,
vitamins. [music] It's got to have fiber
in it. You know what I'm saying? It's
got to make me feel full. You know,
I love rice. Don't get me wrong. I love
rice. Love it. Especially white rice.
But um you know I don't understand hard
gainers. They're like how do you eat so
many calories? It's like how do you eat
so little calorie? Like I don't get
that. I don't get that. You know people
are like oh I was trying to bulk on 3500
calories a day. Oh almost threw up after
every meal. Are you kidding me? I could
eat 3,500 calories in one sitting easy.
I I I could eat 4,000 calories in one
sitting. I I do I've done it many times.
Many times. I mean if I'm going to do
OMAD one meal a day, I'll eat 4,500
calories in one dang meal. Easy. Easy.
Like 250 grams of protein in one meal.
Easy. 600 carbs in one meal. I'm not
even kidding you. I I'm not even kidding
you guys.
[music] So, yeah. My goal is to feel
good, be strong, be lean, have energy.
And for me, rice doesn't really fit into
that, but it might fit into for you. You
might be that kind of guy where you're
like, I just can't eat. You know, if you
just can't eat, then that's fine. Like
Goku was a hard gainer splash films. So,
his trick was speed eating rice. You
know what I'm saying?
You know,
yes, I always take my treadmill on a
leash.
Um [music]
Oh, eggs and sardines for breakfast.
Yeah. Hot giggity. Yeah. Typically, my
breakfast includes eggs and either
mackerel,
some kind of some kind of fatty fish.
either either eggs, fatty fish, or beef
and and some dairy and then whole bunch
of fruits and vegetables.
Yeah, man.
You know, do I train seven days a week?
No, I don't. So, honestly, for me, the
the best the best way I feel is when I
train few days per week. Three
two is two is honestly the way I feel
the best. So, what I do now is I I'm I'm
doing three
Um, which is still pretty good. Still
pretty good. But yeah, I I could never
train seven days a week. I don't know
how people do that. If people are
honestly training seven days a week,
they're probably not really training
very hard at all. I'm I'm I'm too I'm
too driven to train seven days a week.
Uh,
rice has zero sugar. I'm not saying rice
has sugar, Robert Ortiz. Don't
misunderstand me. I'm saying it's it's
literally empty calories. It's calories
for the sake of calories. It it it
doesn't it doesn't like nourish your
body in any way. It's filler food. It'll
keep you alive. It'll keep you alive. It
won't nourish your body is what I'm
trying to say. All right? If you only
ate rice, you would die. All right? If
you only ate potatoes, you would survive
because potatoes will nourish your body.
They have minerals. They have fiber.
They have potassium.
They have vitamins. Rice has been
stripped out. The all the all the fiber
stripped. Everything's just stripped
out. just you might as well eat sugar,
right? Sugar is just a carbohydrate with
no nutritional value. Rice is a
carbohydrate with no nutritional value.
It'll it'll make you gain weight if
you're trying to gain weight. If you
need an extra few calories,
easy rice is the way to go. [music]
Pasta, rice, you know, I could eat two
boxes of pasta. Three boxes, man. I'll
tell you, three boxes of pasta, easy.
Shout out to Smith Grind who's a
carnivore. That's good. You know, if you
feel good as a carnivore, then keep
doing it. Are dates good for you?
They're very good for your marriage. If
you're married, you got to have a date
with your wife at least once a month. At
least where you guys go do something
special. Even it just means you lock the
bedroom door and watch some something
stupid on Netflix.
But seriously,
dates are good. Don't don't don't go
into roommate mode with your wife. All
right? It's not good for your marriage.
And also, um, is the [music] fruit, is
the date actually good for you? Yeah, I
think it's good for you.
I eat dates, you know. Highfat carnivore
diet is good for Smith Grind, then
that's awesome. You know, that's the way
to go. Whatever works [music] for you.
Yeah. Two two days a week full body is
epic.
It really is. Splash Films. Two days a
week full body is epic.
That's that was in general like ever
since I actually started taking lifting
weights seriously, [music] I made most
of my strength and muscle gains on two
days a week. The most basic, you know,
some kind of squat, some kind of hinge,
and then usually it was chin-ups, dips,
uh, rows, and some kind of press, and
then a little [music] bit of arm fluff
at the end. You know what I'm saying?
But yeah. Yeah. two days a week. You
have the drive to work out big time on
that. [music]
You've got that drive.
All right. David is also a highfat
carnivore. We got some high highfat
carnivores in the house. What's up?
Yeah.
my long short. Right now I'm in a little
bit of a short here. You know, right now
I'm in a little bit of a short.
Did a three-day sardine fast. That's
cool. I've heard of that before. I think
from some people in this chat have done
sard sardine fasts.
>> Krypto Crow. Is this really Crypto Crow
in the house? Is this really Cryptocrow?
Hang on a second here.
This really Crypto [music] Crow. Is this
the real Cryptocrow or is this the fake
Crypto Crow? It says official.
Is this really Crypto Crow? Cryptocro.
Is that real you, bro?
What's up, Krypto Crow? If that's real
you, man. God bless you, bro. Thank you
so much for popping in the dang stream.
Honestly, I'm honored if it's real you.
If it's not you, I'm still honored. I'm
honored that all I'm honored that
everybody's here right now. Honestly,
I'm honored that everyone's here right
now.
Are we going to make with this? What are
we going to make with this trade? So,
look, my next Oh, big shout out. It
really is Crypto Crow the official.
What's going on, bro?
Good to see you, man. A longtime
subscriber. I've been subscribed to
Crypto Crow since like 2018 or something
like that. Since the last since I've
been subscribed to Crypto Crow since
before I had a YouTube channel. I've
been subscribed to Crypto Crow.
Since like Yeah, like 2017 18 bull run.
Right around that time.
Right around that time. Man, what's
going on? Good to see you, man.
So, right now, here's the here's the
deal. All right, with this short trade,
my next target is going to be this.
Okay, my first target was this. Okay, so
my first target right here, the golden
pocket. All right, Fibonacci golden
pocket,
right? Right here from the high to the
618. Boom. All right, in the in the in
the in the Discord,
these are our winners here. Let me get
to my my TA channel here.
take the scalp and then at the golden
pocket 131 a few minutes later quick TP.
All right, we're looking for a quick
scalp. Now that the quick scalp is
scalped, the next [music] target is
going to be the bottom of the range. Are
we going to hit it? I have no idea. Do I
care? No. Why don't I care? Cuz I've
already locked in a profit on the trade.
I've already locked in a profit on the
trade. If I get stopped out, I will lose
I will I will get stopped out with an
$800 profit. Okay, so the next target is
the bottom of this mini range here. Now,
do I think we hit it? I have no idea.
I'll be honest. I have no idea. But I
would say this, the 12minute money flow
cross bullish tells me that if we do
come down to this area, we're probably
just going to get a liquidity grab at
the low and then reverse it. Honestly, I
might even look for a long trade if we
come down here. Let me go ahead and set
an alert here.
Let me go ahead and set an alert
right here cuz look at that 12minute
money flow. It's looking juicy as all.
Get out, man. Yeah, Kryptocrow is the
real OG, man.
He is He's a real OG, man. Krypto Crow,
he's been he's been in the space since
since we were all in diapers, man. I'm
telling.
[music]
Fruits make you fatter than rice, says
Robert Ortiz. I don't think any food
makes you fat. Honestly, I don't think
foods make you fat. I think it's all
about energy balance in your body. You
got to figure out what works best for
you. For me, rice does not work. All
right. I would get fat eating rice
because I eat, like I said, I could
literally eat two cups of dry rice. All
right, that's 1,200 calories of rice,
pure carbohydrate, and it would not
satisfy me. All right, I would be hungry
again in like half an hour, right?
[music] So, I don't like rice for that
reason. Fruit, I could stuff my face on
I stuff my face on fruit every single
day.
And guess what? Fruit fills me up. It's
got water. It's got fiber. It's got
micronutrients, [music] you know, it's
got potassium.
It's got a whole bunch of good stuff in
there,
things that your body likes. You eat you
eat a whole bunch of fruit. Do do a
little experiment on yourself. All
right. Eat 1,000 calories of rice. See
how you feel in like an hour. Eat 1,000
calories of fruit. See how you feel in
an hour. You're going to notice the
difference. You're going to feel way
better having eaten all that fruit.
You're going to be hydrated. You're
going to have minerals, vitamins,
you know, it's all that fiber and water
that's going to slow the blood sugar
spike. So, the insulin spike will be
less. You're not going to have that
crash after. Now, of course, I would
never sit down and eat 1,000 calories of
fruit without also having proteins
and some healthy fats. You know what I'm
saying?
But I think as an energy source, fruit
is the way to go. Now, again, that's
just for me. All right? Like remember
guys, I am I'm I am morbidly obese. All
right? I have horrible genetics for
being lean. I was morbidly obese as a
teenager. I was a 5' 3, 185 lb fat
[music] piece of blubber. Okay? Couldn't
even do a push-up.
Couldn't even do a push-up until I was
like 16 years old, man. All right.
If left to my own devices, [music] I am
a fat, weak
person. All right? I'm not the kind of
guy that has trouble getting his
calories, so he needs a little extra
rice preworkout. [music]
I'm not the kind of guy that throws up.
I could eat I could eat like 3,000
calories and go do hill sprints right
after. I'm not going to throw up. My
body needs that food. I'm a fat guy. All
right? So, everyone's different. You
know what I'm saying?
Shout out to Dennis Marv. He says, "Jay,
I noticed when you take trades live, you
go a larger amount and you quickly take
profit before leaving. Do I do that on
scalps?" Yes, if I'm scalping, that's
that's what I do. And the last two
trades I've taken live, that's exactly
what I did cuz honestly, this market's
been chopping me up lately because I've
been holding these trades too dang long.
But yeah, that's what I've been doing,
man. Thank you so much for the for the
uh super chat. You know what I'm saying?
Shout out to Crypto Crow. You guys want
to know about Cardano?
You know,
you got to ask Crypto Crow.
he's the one to ask about the Cardano,
right? I don't know. I still have my
hopes in Cardano. Crypto Crow, should I
hold my Cardano?
Feel like Crypto Crow will say yes.
I feel like Crypto Pro would say yes.
Yes. Just avoid those that identify as
fat. You know, those trans fats.
Yeah, avoid those trans fats, honestly.
Um,
yeah, Cryptocrank is 100% TP kind of
guy. Krypto Crank, man, I have to get
back in your streams, bro. I have not
been on the YouTube.
I have not been watching a lot of crypto
YouTube. I mean, crypto's been boring.
Let's be honest. Go subscribe to
CryptoCrank, guys, if not. [music] All
right. Cryptocrank taking multi-million
dollar scalps.
>> Decides who eats.
>> One or two%,
>> you know. Look, he decides who eats one
or two%. Got the coliseum in here,
>> you know. just due to the uh to the
>> See, he's always got a live trade in
here. Yeah, look, he's got a trade on
right now.
All right, this is He must have uh Hang
on. How much I can't see because of this
stupid thing on here. How much money he
has on the trade.
I He must have already taken profit on
it. He must have already taken profit on
it.
All right, but anyway, go subscribe to
Cryptocrow if you're not subscribed. Go
subscribe.
Go subscribe to Crypto Crow. Crypto
Crank. Basically, here here's the thing.
If it starts with crypto and the next
word starts with a CR, you know it's a
good channel. You know it's a good
channel. All right. Crypto Crow 150,000
subs. All right. Go subscribe. I got to
watch this. This is the video I got to
watch. Honestly, [music]
>> I'm going to put this in my watch later
video.
See how can I How do I do that? Save to
the watch later. There you go. I'm going
to watch this later. Crypto Crow,
I'm going to watch it later.
The stream two days ago, $10 million
position. That's insane, bro. That is
insane. I don't think I've ever had more
than 2.5 million on a pos. I have never
had more than 2.5 million.
[clears throat] Rice and beans and
chicken. That's true, actually. And I do
love me some rice and beans and chicken.
In fact, when I was in Cuba, let me tell
you, all I ate was foes negros. Eros
cono. All right, [music]
I know everyone's shocked with how good
I know my espanol, but seriously,
there's nothing like some good old black
beans and rice with chicken. That is
probably one of my favorite meals of all
time. I'm not even kidding.
And I could I could do some damage, you
know? I could do some damage. I could go
to a Cuban restaurant and eat a family
meal all by myself. I've done it many
times.
Uh, Crypto Crazy made 100K profit stream
from two days ago. Let's check that out.
Stream from two days ago.
Two days ago. There you go.
Dang. All right. Look at that. All
right. He already took profit. He's a
scalper. You You can't go in Crypto
Crank, man. You know, he's a scalper.
It's It's hard to find his trades
because they're so quick.
>> All right.
>> He locked in 30 grand. [music]
>> Let's see.
>> A lot of bagers.
>> Maybe it's right at the beginning.
Maybe it's right at the end.
All right. Well, it's here, guys. It's
here. So, all right. It's here, right?
It's here. It's hard to go back in a
stream and try and find something. It
really is. You know what I'm saying?
Crypto crack. Crypto crash. Yeah, we got
to start we got to start some channels.
Crypto crack. Crypto crash.
Cryptocr official wants to shake
Charles. Just give me a little shake,
you know?
Quit saying those things on Twitter,
man. Like, what the heck, bro?
Crypto crazy.
Wow, we've been live for a while. We've
been live for almost two hours, guys.
You just subscribed to Crypto Crackhead.
I wonder if that's actually a channel.
Let's Let's see. Crypto crackhead.
Cryptocrack.
Yes, Crypto Crackhead. Welcome to my
channel. below under the crypto.
>> All right. Well, we we we'll experience
this [music] together. All right. I
don't want to I don't want to experience
this alone. Okay. I'm a little bit
scared. So, you always feel better when
you experience these types of things
with others. Let's give it a like. Smash
up the likes. Smash up the subscribe.
Crypto crackhead. I wonder if this has
anything to do with crypto.
>> Hello, I am the Crypto Crackhead.
Warning, I am probably not safe for work
or for young children's ears. I am
unquestionably not a financial adviser.
Research is important before investing
your hardearned money. Only spend what
you can afford to lose. Welcome to my
cryptocurrencybased YouTube channel. In
real life, I could be a young, sexy,
beautiful, gorgeous woman, a fat
35year-old man in his mother's basement,
a super advanced AI from the future, or
anything in between. The adventures we
will have. Subscribe and follow me on
Twitter. See you in the blockchain, you
wonderful human being.
[music]
Got to leave a comment here. But you
know what? I think I'm going to
unsubscribe.
I think I'll unsubscribe, but I'll leave
my comment. All right, I'll leave my
comment.
They have one subscriber. It must have
been.
Okay, cool. Eight years ago. Wow. Wow.
Eight years ago.
Wow. Wow. Eight years ago.
Sam Alman's wife.
That's so funny.
Shout out to Eddie. What's going on,
Eddie? Shout out to Crypto Retro.
Shout out to RP Pink.
Why did Moses have his face covered?
You know, my answer is an answer that a
lot of people probably wouldn't agree
with. Bro, I don't know if this is the
right place to talk about it. I don't
know if I want to wax that theological
right now,
but
I I I you know, Paul talks about it in
first Corinthians, 2 Corinthians, I'm
sorry. So I I I think Paul gives the
reason in second Corinthians.
You know,
that's my view.
People say it's cuz they were scared. I
don't think that's what it says. You
know what I'm saying?
If she bought Bitcoin, she's doing good
eight years ago. Yeah. Let's see where
Bitcoin was 8 years ago.
Where was Bitcoin 8 years ago?
It's 2018.
In August,
August 2018, we were
Yeah, he's doing good. 6,500 bucks.
6,500 smackaronis and quesos. Man,
Mondays are like fake moves. What do you
think? Yeah. Yeah, sure. I mean, every
every day is a fake move. I mean, guys,
Bitcoin's been the same price literally
since
uh June. And really, it's been the same
price since February, guys. Bitcoin's
been this price since February. It's
been false move 2026. We've been
chopping around literally the same
price, guys, since July 5th. It's been a
month of literally sideways. Like
literally, it's been a month of
literally sideways,
you know.
So,
shout out to MM MM Lee Bad. I I forget
what this stands for. I used to know.
Um,
yeah. You know what's interesting,
Senor? It doesn't actually give the
reason necessarily as to why he did it,
[clears throat and cough]
which is interesting. It just says that
he did it,
you know.
It's very interesting.
I do think there's a reason,
but I don't want to dive into it here.
Senor, you should definitely have a
Bible channel, bro. Then we can collab
on our own Bible channels. Life is but a
dream. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah, life
is but a dream. Yeah, then we can
collaborate on our Bible channels. You
know, we'll have to uh see.
Billy Casper Bible Channel.
Yeah. Check this one out here. The Billy
Casper Bible Channel. Yeah. You know
what, Senor? If you get yourself a Bible
channel, we will do a collaboration.
We'll do a collaboration, man.
All right. We'll do a collaboration.
Shout out to Johnny. God bless you, bro.
Um, he's going to head out. You know
what, guys? I think I'll head out, too,
cuz we've been live for two hours. And,
uh, yeah, God bless and I'll see you
guys later. Peace.